<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on GRASS GIS - Bringing advanced geospatial technologies to the world</title>
    <link>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on GRASS GIS - Bringing advanced geospatial technologies to the world</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 1998-2019, GRASS Development Team.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:36:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the GRASS GIS team at FOSS4G 2019 </title>
      <link>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/meet-grass-gis-team-at-foss4g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:23:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/meet-grass-gis-team-at-foss4g/</guid>
      <description>This is a test post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new GRASS GIS crowdfunding campaign </title>
      <link>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/new-crowdfunding-campain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 11:36:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/new-crowdfunding-campain/</guid>
      <description>Hey GRASS GIS friends!
We just launched a crowd funding campaign to partially cover the costs of refreshing and re-styling our website https://grass.osgeo.org to newer standards.
Details about our plans for the website migration in 2019 can find on the wiki: https://grasswiki.osgeo.org/wiki/Website_migration_plan_2019
For the realization we need your support, any contribution counts and is most welcome ! You can easily contribute any amount through our PayPal money pool: https://www.paypal.com/pools/c/86YKZiIEPV
Thank you very much for your support</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SVN to GitHub migration has started </title>
      <link>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/svn-migration-has-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 11:36:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nbozon.github.io/GRASS-GIS/news/svn-migration-has-started/</guid>
      <description>SVN to GitHub migration has been started today.
SVN has been set to read-only mode and we are currently updating the new GitHub repos.
We are tracking all efforts here: https://trac.osgeo.org/grass/wiki/GitMigration
Much time of the GRASS GIS Community Sprint Berlin 2019 will be dedicated to complete the migration. Further steps will include: some needed source code updates, migration of trac issues, add labels to the issues in GitHub, migration of the trac wiki, extensive aftermath clean-up (Travis CI/CD setting update, email notifications, IRC notifications, cronjobs, fixing links in the website and grasswiki, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>